Guide to the Amos Alonzo Stagg Papers 1866-1964
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Athletic Associations
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1931 [A] (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1931 [B] (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1932 [A] (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1932 [B] (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1933[A] (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1933 [B] (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1933 [C] (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1934-1935 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1936-1938 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1939-1943 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [N.C.A.A.], 1944-1956 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - N.C.A.A. miscellaneous, football coaches association, 1938-1956 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1946 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 2947 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1951 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1959 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - American Academy of Physical Education, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Post-Chicago Coaching Positions
  - Letters of commendation upon A.A. Stagg's retirement as U. of C. director of athletics, June 30, 1932 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Letters of commendation upon A.A. Stagg's retirement as U. of C. director of athletics, June 30, 1932 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Letters of commendation upon A.A. Stagg's retirement as U. of C. director of athletics, June 30, 1932 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence re A.A.Stagg's consideration and acceptance of G.O.P.'s offer (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence re A.A.Stagg's early 1933 illness, references to Hutchins, U. of C. and future employment (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Apitz, Lawrence (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Athletic department (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Breeden, Robert L. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Francis, Ralph (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Jackson, Earl R. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Knoles, Tully C. [C.O.P. president] (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific - correspondence, Pacific Coast Athletic Conference (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1933 [A] (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1933 [B] (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1946 [A] (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1946 [B] (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific general correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific, biographical information on A.A. Stagg (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, College All-Stars (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, California Aggies (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Chico State (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1934-1935 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1936-1938 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1939-1940 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1941 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1942 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Fresno State, 1946 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Loyola University of Los Angeles (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Notre Dame, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Notre Dame, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Northwestern (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Modesto Junior College (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Pacific Lutheran (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, St. Mary's College (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, San Diego State (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, San Jose State [A] (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, San Jose State [B] (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, San Jose State [C] (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, San Jose State [D] (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Santa Barbara (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, Southern Methodist (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, United States Marines (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Arizona (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of California (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of California Ramblers (B team) (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Chicago (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Hawaii (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Nevada (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Oregon (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Southern California [A] (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Southern California [B] (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - College of the Pacific, scouting reports, University of Southern California [C] (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1935 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1936 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1937 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1938 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - College of the Pacific - mimeographed game handouts, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, A-D (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, E-H (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, I-O (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, P-Q (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, R-S (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Susquehanna University - correspondence, T-Z (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Stockton College football (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Series VII: Biographical
  - Biographical--general (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Biographical--general (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Biographical--general (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Biographical--general (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Biographical data, notes, and letters (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Battle Creek Sanitarium, 1907 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Athletics and Athletic Training - proposed book, 1916 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Chicago World's Fair, 1933 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Biographical clippings, ca. 1935 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Tale reunion [class of 1888] and Minneapolis track meet, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg's 50th year of coaching, 1939 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Stagg's Day in Chicago, June 1-5, 1955 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Honorary degrees (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Proposed motion pictures of A.A. Stagg's life (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Jester's Club (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Who' Who in American sports (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Chamber of Commerce - national and local (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - A.A. Stagg High School, Stockton, California (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Big ten clubs of California (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Articles on A.A. Stagg (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Articles on A.A. Stagg (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, A-B (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, C-D (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, E-G (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, H-K (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, Longman, Green and Company, 1926-1930 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, L-M (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, N-R (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, Stout, Wesley W. (Saturday Evening Post) (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, S-T (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, U-Z (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Touchdown - manuscripts, corrected manuscripts for Saturday Evening Post series (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Touchdown - manuscripts, series in the Saturday Evening Post (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Touchdown - correspondence, miscellaneous notes and printed materials (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Allied Forces on Prohibition, A.A. Stagg, chairman (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Allied Forces on Prohibition, testimonial luncheon for Daniel Poling (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Stagg's testimony in support of the 18th amendment, 1926-1930 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Letters if commendation to A.A. Stagg for U.S. Senate sub-committee appearance, April 17, 1926 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco - Killer of youth (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Tobacco - Killer of youth (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Tobacco - Killer of youth (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, American Physical Ed. Association (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Area Project (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Big Brother Assn. (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Christian Athletes, Inc. (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Committee of Fifteen (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Committee of 1,000 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Committee on Social Analysis of College Communities (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Committee of Thirty-one (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Daughters of the American Constitution (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Fellowship of Christian Athletes (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Governor's Commission on Unemployment (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Hyde Park Baptist Church (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Men of America Club (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, National Athletic Conference (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Quetico-Superior Council (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Sixty-Five Club (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Sportsmanship Brotherhood (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, Western Society for the Suppression of Vice (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, White House Conference on Child Health Care and Protection (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Civic and philanthropic associations, University of Chicago, Y.M.C.A. (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1892-1899 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1900 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1901-1907 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1908-1910 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1911-1912 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1913 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1914-1916 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1917-1920 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1921-1922 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1923 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, 1924 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1924-1926 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1925 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1926 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1927 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1928 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1929 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1930 [A] (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1930 [B] (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1931 [A] (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1931 [B] (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1931 [C] (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1932 [A] (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1932 [B] (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1932 [C] (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1933 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1934-1940 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - A.A. Stagg speeches, articles, requests for articles, observations and notes, clippings from and about speeches, Development campaign of 1940-1954 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1923 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1925 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1926 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1927 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1928 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1929 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1933 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1934 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1935 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1936 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1938 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1940 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1941 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1942 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1945 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1946 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Selected clippings re A.A. Stagg, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Honorary Associations - Basketball Hall of Fame (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Associations - Football Hall of Fame (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Associations - Helm's Hall of Fame (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1952 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1952 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1952 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1954 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1954 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1954 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1954 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1955 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1955 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1955 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [A-C] (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [D-F] (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [H-L] (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [M-P] (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [R-T] (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1956 [W-Z] (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [A-B] (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [C-F] (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [G-L] (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [M-O] (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [P-R] (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [S] (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1957 [T-Z] (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [A-B] (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [C-F] (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [G-J] (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [K-M] (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [N-R] (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Birthday, Anniversary, Christmas, New Year, get Well cards, etc., 1958 [R-W] (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - This box includes a glass lantern slide of a University of Chicago two mile run, 1901, colored glass plate slide of the University of Chicago and the Midway, and photo albums of 1914 University of Chicago Field Day celebrations and the 1922 Chicago vs. Princeton football game. (Box 118)
  - This box includes ticket stubs, schedules and passes for University of Chicago, White Sox and Cubs games, a Skull and Bones directory, school compositions and atlas, Yale almanacs and class books, Yale notebooks, songbooks, history of football and banquet programs and photos of the 1887 and 1888 Yale football team. (Box 119)
  - Contains two red tablecloths used on the 1894 U. of Chicago football team trip to California to play Stanford University (Box 120)
  - Contains handbooks, committee programs, constitutions and by-laws, statistics and minutes for various universities, athletic associations, interscholastic programs and the YMCA. (Box 121)